http://www.pfeiffer.edu/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Request Information
Ready to find out more about Pfeiffer University? Tell us about yourself and you’ll be on your way.
First, tell us what type of student you are:
Phone Number *
Please input your phone, including area code, ex: (704) 555-5555
Email Address *
Address *
City *
State *
SelectAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
Zip Code *
Please indicate your student type and anticipated start date.
Start Date *
- Select -Fall 2015Spring 2016Summer 2016Fall 2016Spring 2017Summer 2017Fall 2017Spring 2018Summer 2018Fall 2018Spring 2019Summer 2019Fall 2019Spring 2020Summer 2020
Field of Study *
- Select -Business Management and Leadership - B.S.Criminal Justice - B.S.Health Administration - B.S.Human Relations - B.A.Interdisciplinary Studies - B.A.Registered Nurse to Bachelor of Science in NursingBusiness Administration - MBAEducation - MSEFinancial Fraud - MSFFIHealth Administration - MHALeadership - MSLMarriage and Family Therapy - MMFTPractical Theology - MAPTTeaching (Special Education) - MAT-SPED
Student Type *
- Select -UndergraduateGraduateDegree CompletionProfessional CertificateOther...
Please Specify
Send Request
Apply Now
Ready to apply to Pfeiffer University?
Tell us about yourself and you’ll be on your way.
First, tell us what type of student you are:
Undergraduate Programs
Graduate Programs
Degree Completion
Professional Certificates
Show Mobile Menu
Hide Mobile Menu
Privacy Policy
You are hereHomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
© Copyright 2016 Pfeiffer University. All Rights Reserved.
Office of Enrollment Management Privacy Statement
Pfeiffer University Enrollment Services recognizes that privacy is important.
Our policy is to protect the privacy and confidentiality of individuals accessing our website and/or submitting information to the Office of Admission. Additional policies related to personal information are outlined in the Pfeiffer University Employee Handbook and the Information Technology Resources Acceptable Use Policy.
Personal Information
Pfeiffer University Admissions collects personal information when you inquire about specific programs and/or apply for admissions to any of our programs (graduate, undergraduate, degree completion). We collect this information to serve your needs such as responding to your inquiry or processing your application for admissions. This may involve redirecting your information to another campus employee or department to better suit your needs.
When you visit our website, we do not collect personal information about you. In particular we do not use “cookies” to collect or store personal information. We do analyze general information about web traffic and click-through patterns through Google Analytics. We do not send personal information to Google Analytics. The Pfeiffer University website is hosted with Pantheon.
We use Google Analytics to evaluate accessibility or gauge popularity of various features on our website and evaluate web traffic to determine which pages are effective and attract the most interest. We also use that information for general reporting and management functions. Specifically we use analytic tools to generate statistics, determine technical design specifications and identify system performance issues.
All information collected from our website, including server logs and information collected from forms or emails you send us, is not actively shared. However, in some cases we may be required by law to release information to help law enforcement investigations, legal proceedings or internal investigations. We may use third party vendors to process your information. We require that all third party vendors utilize appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
Enrollment Services Access
When you submit an inquiry or application to Pfeiffer University, certain staff members have access to that information. The enrollment management staff is made up of undergraduate, graduate and degree completion enrollment personnel. The enrollment staff maintains privacy of data stored or sent using appropriate technology resources. This privacy is maintained in accordance with university policies and local, state and federal laws. We do not sell or distribute any personal information unless required by law.
The Office of Admissions maintains privacy of data stored or sent using its technology resources. This privacy is maintained in accordance with university policies and local, state and federal laws.
Pfeiffer University
How to Apply
Visit Campus
Campus Map
Contact Us
Giving to Pfeiffer
Public Services
State Authorization
© Copyright 2016 Pfeiffer University. All Rights Reserved.
Apply Now
Request Information
Visit Campus
